const questions = [
    {
      lang: "javascript",
      questions: [
        {
          question: "Which of the following is not JavaScript Data Types?",
          opt_1: "Undefined",
          opt_2: "Number",
          opt_3: "Boolean",
          opt_4: "Float",
          correctAnswer: "Float",
        },
        {
          question: "Which company developed JavaScript?",
          opt_1: "Netscape",
          opt_2: "Bell Labs",
          opt_3: "Sun Microsystems",
          opt_4: "IBM",
          correctAnswer: "Netscape",
        },
        {
          question: "Inside which HTML element do we put the JavaScript?",
          opt_1: "<script>",
          opt_2: "<head>",
          opt_3: "<meta>",
          opt_4: "<style>",
          correctAnswer: "<script>",
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is correct about features of JavaScript?",
          opt_1: "It can not Handling dates and time.",
          opt_2: "JavaScript is a object-based scripting language.",
          opt_3: "JavaScript is not interpreter based scripting language.",
          opt_4: "All of the above",
          correctAnswer: "JavaScript is a object-based scripting language.",
        },
        {
          question: "Choose the correct JavaScript syntax to change the content of the following HTML code.",
          opt_1: "document.getElement (\"letsfindcourse\").innerHTML = \"I am a letsfindcourse\";",
          opt_2: "document.getElementById (\"letsfindcourse\").innerHTML = \"I am a letsfindcourse\"",
          opt_3: "document.getId (\"letsfindcourse\") = \"I am a letsfindcourse\";",
          opt_4: "document.getElementById (\"letsfindcourse\").innerHTML = I am a letsfindcourse;",
          correctAnswer: "document.getElementById (\"letsfindcourse\").innerHTML = \"I am a letsfindcourse\"",
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is the correct syntax to display \"Letsfindcourse\" in an alert box using JavaScript?",
          opt_1: "alert-box(\"Letsfindcourse\");",
          opt_2: "confirm(\"Letsfindcourse\");",
          opt_3: " msgbox(\"Letsfindcourse\");",
          opt_4: "alert(\"Letsfindcourse\");",
          correctAnswer: "alert(\"Letsfindcourse\");",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called \"LFC.js\"?",
          opt_1: "<script src=\"LFC.js\">",
          opt_2: "<script source=\"LFC.js\">",
          opt_3: "<script ref=\"LFC.js\">",
          opt_4: "<script type=\"LFC.js\">",
          correctAnswer: "<script src=\"LFC.js\">",
        },
        {
          question: "Which of the following is not Javascript frameworks or libraries?",
          opt_1: "Polymer",
          opt_2: "Meteor",
          opt_3: "Cassandra",
          opt_4: "jQuery",
          correctAnswer: "Cassandra",
        },
        {
          question: "Why so JavaScript and Java have similar name?",
          opt_1: "JavaScript is a stripped-down version of Java",
          opt_2: "JavaScript's syntax is loosely based on Java's",
          opt_3: "They both originated on the island of Java",
          opt_4: "None of the above",
          correctAnswer: "JavaScript's syntax is loosely based on Java's",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the original name of JavaScript?",
          opt_1: "LiveScript",
          opt_2: "EScript",
          opt_3: "Mocha",
          opt_4: "JavaScript",
          correctAnswer: "Mocha",
        },
        {
          question: "JavaScript is designed for following purpose -",
          opt_1: "to style HTML pages",
          opt_2: "to execute Queries related to databases on a server",
          opt_3: "to add interactivity to html pages",
          opt_4: "All of the above",
          correctAnswer: "All of the above",
        },
        {
          question: `What will be the output of the following Javascript code?
                    var string1 = "Letsfindcourse";
                    var intvalue = 30;
                    alert( string1 + intvalue );
          `,
          opt_1: "Letsfindcourse 30",
          opt_2: "30",
          opt_3: "Letsfindcourse30",
          opt_4: "Exception",
          correctAnswer: "Letsfindcourse30",
        },
      ],
    },
    {
      lang: "css",
      questions: {
        question: "AAAAA",
        options: ["op_1", "op_2", "pp_3"],
        correctAnswer: "op_2",
      },
    },
    {
      lang: "html",
      questions: {
        question: "AAAAA",
        options: ["op_1", "op_2", "pp_3"],
        correctAnswer: "op_2",
      },
    },
    {
      lang: "nodejs",
      questions: {
        question: "AAAAA",
        options: ["op_1", "op_2", "pp_3"],
        correctAnswer: "op_2",
      },
    },
    {
      lang: "reactjs",
      questions: {
        question: "AAAAA",
        options: ["op_1", "op_2", "pp_3"],
        correctAnswer: "op_2",
      },
    },
  ];
  
  export default questions;